'Going for a walk' is a popular pastime among older and younger generations alike because of its well-known benefits for our physical and mental health.
"去散步"是受老年人和年轻人欢迎的休闲方式，因为它对我们的身心健康有着众所周知的好处。
But you may be surprised to hear that meandering through pretty streets or hiking along mountainous ridges have not always been considered leisure activities, according to Daniel Gale, a researcher of pedestrianism.
但根据步行运动研究者丹尼尔·盖尔的说法，听到漫步于美丽的街道或沿着山脊徒步并非一直被视为休闲活动，你可能会感到惊讶。
He says that in Britain, walking for fun "wasn't really a thing" until the 1780s.
他说，在英国，为乐趣而散步直到18世纪80年代才真正流行起来。
Before that, it was just something people did out of necessity, and some people associated it with criminal activity.
在此之前，散步只是人们出于需要而做的事，有些人还将其与犯罪活动联系在一起。
But for Charles Dickens, the famous English 19th Century author, marching through London streets and tramping around the countryside was a big part of the creative process; a time to absorb what was going on around him.
但对于19世纪英国著名作家查尔斯·狄更斯来说，快步行走于伦敦街头和在乡间徒步是创作过程中的重要部分；是了解周围事物发生的时刻。
He walked at an impressive pace of four miles per hour, according to his biography by Peter Ackroyd.
根据彼得·阿克罗伊德的传记，他以每小时四英里的惊人速度行走。
But if speed-walking isn't your thing, perhaps you can take inspiration from another big-thinking wanderer.
但如果快走不是你的风格，也许你可以从另一位深思熟虑的漫步者那里获得灵感。
19th Century American writer Henry David Thoreau took a slower approach, preferring to saunter over hills and fields and meander through the woods.
19世纪美国作家亨利·戴维·梭罗采用了较慢的方式，更喜欢在丘陵和田野间闲逛，在树林中蜿蜒漫步。
He said that he could not preserve his health and spirits, unless he spent four hours a day walking at least.
他说，除非每天至少步行四个小时，否则他无法保持健康和活力。
This idea of taking a stroll to clear your head has survived through to the 21st Century, but has pedestrian etiquette remained the same?
这种通过散步来使头脑清醒的观点一直延续到了21世纪，但步行礼仪是否保持不变呢？
A 1780 article for the London Magazine advised pedestrians to avoid things such as loitering in conversation and obstructing people behind you with a "sauntering gait".
1780年《伦敦杂志》的一篇文章建议行人避免诸如在交谈中闲逛，以及用"漫步的步态"阻挡身后的人。
Nowadays, we could probably add distracted phone-users to that list.
如今，我们可能还要把分心的手机使用者添加到这个清单中。
In this modern age, when many of us are tied to our desks and to our screens, the simple act of stepping out onto the city pavements, or getting lost in nature, may make all the difference to our wellbeing.
在这个现代时代，当我们许多人被束缚在办公桌和屏幕前时，走到城市的人行道上，或者迷失在大自然中，这一简单举动可能对我们的福祉产生重大影响。
Whether you see yourself more as a casual stroller or a purposeful strider, why not build a habit out of it?
无论你视自己为随意的漫步者还是目标明确的大步行走者，何不将它养成一种习惯呢？